Finding Aid for Buck Family papers, 1851-1928
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Buck Family papers 1851-1928
Buck Family.
3 microfilm rolls (1 linear foot)
85839 mf 309c, mf 310c, mf 311c
Settlers in Englishville, Michigan. Family correspondence, diaries, legal papers, newspaper clippings and other materials relating to farm life, personal affairs, and the Civil War.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was given to the Bentley Historical Library by Roy and Owen Holmes in 1967 (donor no. 844 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The Buck family lived in Englishville, Kent County, Michigan. One member of the family, Curtis Buck, served in Battery B, 1st Light Artillery, during the Civil War. Another member, Andrew N. Buck, served with 1st and 7th Michigan Cavalry.
The Buck family collection includes correspondence, diaries, legal papers, newspaper clippings, and other materials relating to farm life, personal affairs, and the Civil War. Included are letters of Curtis Buck and Andrew Buck relating to the Civil War. Also of interest is a letter of John Bettis, June 10, 1864, regarding his running a saw and grist mill in Chattanooga during the war. Other family members represented in the collection are Charles W. Buck and Myron and Susan Field Buck.
Subjects:
Buck family.; Englishville (Mich.); Farm life--Michigan--Kent County.; Farmers--Michigan--Kent County.; Field family.; Kent County (Mich.); Farmers--Religious life--Michigan--Kent County.; Soldiers--Michigan--Kent County.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865.; United States. Army. Michigan Artillery Regiment, 1st (1861-1865). Battery B.; United States. Army. Michigan Cavalry Regiment, 1st (1861-1866). Company M.; United States. Army. Michigan Cavalry Regiment, 7th (1862-1865). Company F.; United States. Army. Michigan Engineers and Mechanics Regiment, 1st (1861-1865). Company D.; Gettysburg, Battle of, Gettysburg, Pa., 1863.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Buck, Andrew Newton, b. 1839.; Buck family.; Dwellings--Ohio--Toledo.; Toledo (Ohio)--Dwellings.
Contributors:
Bettis, John T., b. 1839.; Buck, Andrew Newton, b. 1839.; Buck, Charles W.; Buck, Curtis, b. 1841.; Buck, Myron.; Buck, Susan Field.
Genre Terms:
Diaries.; Photographs.
- Correspondence
  - 1851-1861 (Reel 1)
  - 1862 (Reel 1)
  - 1863 (Reel 1)
  - 1864 (Reel 1)
  - 1865-1869 (Reel 1)
  - 1870-1876 (Reel 1)
  - 1881-1885 (Reel 1)
  - 1886-1888 (Reel 1)
  - 1889-1890 (Reel 1)
  - 1891-1896 (Reel 1)
  - 1897-1899 (Reel 1)
  - 1901-1904 (Reel 1)
  - 1905 (Reel 1)
  - 1906 (Reel 1)
  - 1907 (Reel 2)
  - 1908-1909 (Reel 2)
  - 1910 (Reel 2)
  - 1911 (Reel 2)
  - 1912 (Reel 2)
  - 1913-1914 (Reel 2)
  - 1915 (Reel 2)
  - 1916 (Reel 2)
  - 1917 (Reel 2)
  - 1918 (Reel 2)
  - 1919 (Reel 2)
  - 1920 (Reel 2)
  - 1921 (Reel 2)
  - 1922 (Reel 2)
  - 1923-1928 (Reel 2)
  - Undated (Reel 2)
- Other materials
  - Essays by Myron Buck (Reel 3)
  - Miscellaneous deeds, agreements, etc., ca. 1836-1906 (Reel 3)
  - Buck family genealogical material (Reel 3)
  - Photographs (Reel 3)
    (portraits and photo of family home in Toledo, Ohio)